<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<EntityExport><aWLI_StateProvision><States Id="1"><![CDATA[Undefined,AK,AL,AR,AZ,CA,CO,CT,DE,FL,GA,HI,IA,ID,IL,IN,KS,KY,LA,MA,MD,ME,MI,MN,MO,MS,MT,NC,ND,NE,NH,NJ,NM,NV,NY,OH,OK,OR,PA,RI,SC,SD,TN,TX,UT,VA,VT,WA,WI,WV,WY,AS,DC,FM,GU,MH,MP,PW,PR,VI]]></States><Code Id="2"><![CDATA[BCF]]></Code><content Id="4"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\deff0\deflang1036{\fonttbl{\f0\fswiss\fprq2\fcharset0 Calibri;}{\f1\froman\fprq2\fcharset2 Symbol;}{\f2\fnil MS Sans Serif;}}
{\colortbl ;\red0\green0\blue0;}
\viewkind4\uc1\pard\sl276\slmult1\lang1033\b\f0\fs22 SECTION I -- GENERAL BUILDING FORM\par
\b0 The Company will pay for direct physical loss of or damage to covered property at the premises described in the Declarations caused by or resulting from any cause of loss or damage covered under this form. \par
\par
\b I. PROPERTY COVERED\par
\b0 BUILDING(S): Building(s) or structure(s) shall include attached additions and extensions; fixtures, machinery and equipment constituting a permanent part of and pertaining to the service of the building(s); materials and supplies intended for use in construction, alteration or repair of the building(s) or structure(s); yard fixtures; personal property of the insured used for the maintenance or service of the building(s), including fire extinguishing apparatus, outdoor furniture, floor coverings and appliances for refrigerating, ventilating, cooking, dishwashing and laundering (but not including other personal property in apartments or rooms furnished by the named insured as landlord); all while at the designated premises.\par
\par
\b II. PROPERTY NOT COVERED\par
\b0 THIS POLICY DOES NOT COVER:\par
\pard\fi-360\li720\sl276\slmult1\f1\'b7\tab A. \f0 Outdoor swimming pools; fences; piers, wharves and docks; beach or diving platforms or appurtenances; retaining walls not constituting a part of a building; walks, roadways and other paved surfaces.\par
\f1\'b7\tab\f0 B. Outdoor signs, whether or not attached to a building or structure.\par
\f1\'b7\tab\f0 C. Lawns; outdoor trees, shrubs and plants except as provided in the Extensions And Limitations Of Coverage.\par
\par
\pard\sl276\slmult1\b IV. PERILS INSURED AGAINST\par
\b0 This policy insures against all direct loss or damage to the property covered under this form caused by:\par
\par
\pard\fi-360\li1068\sl276\slmult1 A.FIRE.\par
\pard\li1068\sl276\slmult1\par
\pard\li708\sl276\slmult1 B. LIGHTNING.\par
\par
C. WINDSTORM OR HAIL, excluding loss or damage caused directly or indirectly by frost or cold weather, or ice (other than hail), snow or sleet, whether driven by wind or not.\par
\pard\li2832\sl276\slmult1\par
\pard\li708\sl276\slmult1 D. EXPLOSION, including direct loss or damage resulting from the explosion of accumulated gases or unconsumed fuel within the firebox (or combustion chamber) of any fired vessel or within the flues or passages which conduct the gases of combustion therefrom.\par
\pard\li2124\sl276\slmult1\par
\pard\li708\sl276\slmult1 E. SMOKE, meaning sudden and accidental loss or damage from smoke, other than smoke\par
from agricultural smudging or industrial operations.\par
\par
F. AIRCRAFT OR VEHICLES, meaning only direct loss or damage resulting from actual physical contact of an aircraft or a vehicle with the property covered or with the building(s) containing the property covered, except that loss or damage by aircraft\par
includes direct loss or damage by objects falling therefrom.\par
\pard\sl276\slmult1\lang1036\par
\pard\cf1\f2\fs16\par
}
]]></content><Clausetype Id="1"><![CDATA[General provision]]></Clausetype><Title Id="1"><![CDATA[Apartment Building-Building Coverage Form]]></Title><EnumerateSubDocuments Id="14"><![CDATA[No]]></EnumerateSubDocuments><SecondaryDocument Id="17"><![CDATA[No]]></SecondaryDocument><DuringComposition Id="4"><![CDATA[Mandatory]]></DuringComposition><Composed Id="15"><![CDATA[No]]></Composed><Numerotation Id="29"><![CDATA[(0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0)]]></Numerotation><Level Id="30"><![CDATA[0]]></Level><StartOnNextpage Id="36"><![CDATA[No]]></StartOnNextpage><Name Id="3"><![CDATA[Apartment Building-Building Coverage Form]]></Name><MigrationDate Id="15"><![CDATA[--/--/----]]></MigrationDate><NSId Id="1"><![CDATA[318775697]]></NSId><Id Id="2"><![CDATA[3]]></Id><Version Id="3"><![CDATA[1]]></Version></aWLI_StateProvision></EntityExport>