<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<EntityExport><aWLI_StateProvision><States Id="1"><![CDATA[Undefined,AK,AL,AR,AZ,CA,CO,CT,DE,FL,GA,HI,IA,ID,IL,IN,KS,KY,LA,MA,MD,ME,MI,MN,MO,MS,MT,NC,ND,NE,NH,NJ,NM,NV,NY,OH,OK,OR,PA,RI,SC,SD,TN,TX,UT,VA,VT,WA,WI,WV,WY,AS,DC,FM,GU,MH,MP,PW,PR,VI]]></States><Code Id="2"><![CDATA[BIF]]></Code><content Id="4"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\deff0\deflang1036{\fonttbl{\f0\fnil\fcharset0 Arial;}{\f1\fnil\fcharset0 Arial,Bold;}{\f2\fswiss\fprq2\fcharset0 Calibri;}}
\viewkind4\uc1\pard\lang1033\fs20 Business Income means the:\par
\b\f1 a. \b0\f0 Net Income (Net Profit or Loss before income taxes) that would have been earned or incurred; and\par
\b\f1 b. \b0\f0 Continuing normal operating expenses incurred, including payroll.\par
For manufacturing risks, Net Income includes the net sales value of production.\par
Coverage is provided as described and limited below for one or more of the following options for which a Limit of Insurance is shown in the Declarations.\par
\par
We will pay for the actual loss of Business Income you sustain due to the necessary "suspension" of your "operations" during the "period of restoration".\par
The "suspension" must be caused by direct physical loss of or damage to property at premises which are described in the Declarations and for which a Business Income Limit of Insurance is shown in the Declarations. The loss or damage\par
must be caused by or result from a Covered Cause of Loss. With respect to loss of or damage to personal property in the open or personal property in a vehicle, the described premises include the area within 100 feet of the site at which the described\par
premises are located.\par
\f2\fs22\par
\b\f1\fs20 Covered Causes Of Loss, Exclusions And Limitations\par
\b0\f0 See applicable Causes of Loss Form as shown in the Declarations.\par
\par
\b\f1 Additional Limitation . Interruption Of Computer Operations\par
\b0\f0 Coverage for Business Income does not apply when a "suspension" of "operations" is caused by destruction or corruption of electronic data, or any loss or damage to electronic data, except as provided under the Additional Coverage . Interruption Of Computer Operations.\f2\fs22\par
}
]]></content><Clausetype Id="1"><![CDATA[General provision]]></Clausetype><Title Id="1"><![CDATA[Apartment Building-Business Income Form]]></Title><EnumerateSubDocuments Id="14"><![CDATA[No]]></EnumerateSubDocuments><SecondaryDocument Id="17"><![CDATA[No]]></SecondaryDocument><DuringComposition Id="4"><![CDATA[Mandatory]]></DuringComposition><Composed Id="15"><![CDATA[No]]></Composed><Numerotation Id="29"><![CDATA[(0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0)]]></Numerotation><Level Id="30"><![CDATA[0]]></Level><StartOnNextpage Id="36"><![CDATA[No]]></StartOnNextpage><Name Id="3"><![CDATA[Apartment Building-Business Income Form]]></Name><MigrationDate Id="15"><![CDATA[--/--/----]]></MigrationDate><NSId Id="1"><![CDATA[318775697]]></NSId><Id Id="2"><![CDATA[4]]></Id><Version Id="3"><![CDATA[1]]></Version></aWLI_StateProvision></EntityExport>