<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<EntityExport><aWLI_StateProvision><States Id="1"><![CDATA[Undefined,AK,AL,AR,AZ,CA,CO,CT,DE,FL,GA,HI,IA,ID,IL,IN,KS,KY,LA,MA,MD,ME,MI,MN,MO,MS,MT,NC,ND,NE,NH,NJ,NM,NV,NY,OH,OK,OR,PA,RI,SC,SD,TN,TX,UT,VA,VT,WA,WI,WV,WY,AS,DC,FM,GU,MH,MP,PW,PR,VI]]></States><Code Id="2"><![CDATA[P11]]></Code><content Id="4"><![CDATA[GROUP LONG TERM DISABILITY INSURANCE

W INSURANCE COMPANY Life is pleased to underwrite Your Group Long Term Disability Insurance Benefits.  We welcome You to W INSURANCE COMPANY and hope that we can be assistance to You in the future.

A brief explanation of the Plan is as follows:

THE BENEFITS OF THE PLAN
This Plan is being provided by Your Employer to ensure ongoing compensation if You become disabled.
The Plan provides for a benefit to be payable to You after You have been disabled for a certain length of time.  This time period is referred to as the Elimination Period and is shown on Your Certificate's Schedule of Benefits.
The amount payable under the Plan is shown on Your Certificate's Schedule of Benefits.

BENEFITS PAYABLE
Once an employee has become disabled and the disability satisfies Us that it meets the Policy definition of Disability, the benefits will be payable monthly after the Elimination Period is completed, and will be paid until the expiration of the Benefit Pe
riod shown on Your Certificate's Schedule of Benefits or upon attainment of reaching the maximum age for coverage (stated on the Certificate's Schedule of Benefits); whichever is the earlier.
OTHER INCOME BENEFITS 
The Monthly Income Benefit as expressed in the Certificate's Schedule of Benefits shall be reduced by the following other types of income payments which You may be entitled under:
a)	Any Workmen's Compensation Act or any other Act of Law of like intent:
b)	Any disability income benefits for which You are eligible, namely:
i)	Any other group insurance,
ii)	Any retirement plan;
iii)	Any Government retirement or disability plan;
iv)	Any Social Security Benefits
v)	Any earnings received from any form of employment, except as permitted under the Rehabilitative Benefit.
EVIDENCE OF GOOD HEALTH
When You are initially enrolled into the Plan, You may be added for the minimum amount of insurance which can be supplied without evidence of good health.  Upon completion of the medical underwriting and once approved by Us, Your benefit amount will be in
creased to provide the coverage levels shown for Your classification.
From time to time, additional medical underwriting may be required due to Your salary being increased.  Before the insured monthly benefit amount can be adjusted to reflect Your higher earnings, We may require further evidence of good health.  If the addi
tional evidence is approved, the higher benefit amount will become effective from the first of the month following Our acceptance.

ELIMINATION PERIOD
Elimination Period means the period of time (as stated in the Certificate's Schedule of Benefits) which must elapse after the commencement of each period of Total Disability before any Monthly Income Benefit is payable.

DEFINITION OF DISABILITY
During the first two years (exclusive of the Elimination Period) of disability, You will be considered totally disabled if You cannot perform the duties of Your own occupation.  However, after this period, You will be considered totally disabled if the di
sability prevents You from performing the duties of any occupation for which You are reasonably fitted by training, education or experience.
Recurrent Total Disability
If, after treatment of any Total Disability, You again become totally disabled from the same or related cause, this later period of Total Disability shall be considered a continuation of the previous period of Total Disability if You have returned to acti
ve, full-time employment for a period of less than six consecutive months.
Pre-EXISTING CONDITIONS
We will not pay Monthly Benefits for any period of disability which results directly or indirectly, from an injury or sickness for which during the twelve months immediately prior to the Effective Date, You:
-	received medical treatment
-	took prescription drugs
-	consulted a Physician
-	incurred medical expenses
-	received care or services
-	experienced symptoms
This limitation will not apply to a period of disability which begins more than 12 consecutive months after the most recent Effective Date of Your insurance.
RehabiliTation
If You become Totally Disabled from Your regular occupation but accept rehabilitative employment, We will continue to pay the Monthly Income Benefit less 50% of any remuneration received from the rehabilitative employment.  This Monthly Income Benefit wil
l be paid up to 24 months or up to the own occupation period or to the time when the Monthly Income Benefits would normally cease, whichever is the earlier.
Monthly Income Benefits will be further reduced so that the Monthly Benefits payable under the Policy plus Your income received from rehabilitative employment earnings and all other sources does not exceed 100% of Your pre-disability gross earnings from Y
our Employer.
]]></content><Clausetype Id="1"><![CDATA[General provision]]></Clausetype><Title Id="1"><![CDATA[Long Term Disability]]></Title><EnumerateSubDocuments Id="14"><![CDATA[No]]></EnumerateSubDocuments><SecondaryDocument Id="17"><![CDATA[No]]></SecondaryDocument><DuringComposition Id="4"><![CDATA[Mandatory]]></DuringComposition><Composed Id="15"><![CDATA[No]]></Composed><Numerotation Id="29"><![CDATA[(0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0)]]></Numerotation><Level Id="30"><![CDATA[0]]></Level><StartOnNextpage Id="36"><![CDATA[No]]></StartOnNextpage><Name Id="3"><![CDATA[Group Life-Long Term]]></Name><MigrationDate Id="15"><![CDATA[--/--/----]]></MigrationDate><NSId Id="1"><![CDATA[318775697]]></NSId><Id Id="2"><![CDATA[26]]></Id><Version Id="3"><![CDATA[1]]></Version></aWLI_StateProvision></EntityExport>