<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<EntityExport><aWLI_StateProvision><States Id="1"><![CDATA[Undefined,AK,AL,AR,AZ,CA,CO,CT,DE,FL,GA,HI,IA,ID,IL,IN,KS,KY,LA,MA,MD,ME,MI,MN,MO,MS,MT,NC,ND,NE,NH,NJ,NM,NV,NY,OH,OK,OR,PA,RI,SC,SD,TN,TX,UT,VA,VT,WA,WI,WV,WY,AS,DC,FM,GU,MH,MP,PW,PR,VI]]></States><Code Id="2"><![CDATA[P8]]></Code><content Id="4"><![CDATA[GROUP LIFE INSURANCE

Welcome to W INSURANCE COMPANY Life:
W INSURANCE COMPANY Life is pleased to underwrite Your Group Life Insurance which is provided by Your Employer.  We welcome You to W INSURANCE COMPANY and hope that we can be of assistance and help to You in the future.
A brief explanation of the Plan is as follows:

GROUP LIFE BENEFITS
The Benefits You are entitled to under the Plan are as stated in Your Certificate of Benefits.  When You first join the Plan, Your coverage may be limited to the amount of coverage which can be provided without evidence of good health. This automatic cover is sometimes referred to as "non-evidence medical limit".  Once You have satisfied the necessary medical underwriting requirements and have been approved by Us, Your coverage will be increased accordingly from the first of the month after medical approval.  When the higher coverage is accepted, You will receive a revised Certificate which will show the increased coverage.

ONGOING MEDICAL REQUIREMENTS
From time to time, additional evidence of good health may be required as a result of salary increases.  If your salary adjustment is subject to further evidence of good health, the increase will go into effect the first of the month following our acceptance.

MAXIMUM SUM ASSURED
A Maximum Sum Assured is placed on the Plan.  This amount is shown on the Certificate's Schedule of Benefits.

BENEFICIARY
You are required to name a beneficiary to receive the insurance benefits upon Your death and this designation is originally made when You complete Your enrolment card.  If at any time You wish to change this beneficiary designation, please ask Your Employer for a Change of Beneficiary Card for completion and have Your Employer submit this change to Us.  Upon receipt, We will amend Our records and provide You with a revised Certificate stating the change.

PAYMENT OF THE BENEFITS UPON DEATH
The sum assured is normally paid in a lump sum.  However, at Your Beneficiary's request, the proceeds can be paid in fixed monthly installments.

ACCELERATED DEATH BENEFITS
You can apply for up to 50% of your Sum Insured subject to a maximum of $50,000 if You are diagnosed with a terminal illness and You are not expected to survive more than 12 months from the request of payment of the Accelerated Death Benefits.
DISABLED WHILST COVERED UNDER THIS PLAN
If while insured under this Plan, You become totally disabled prior to age 65 years, Your Sum Insured at the time of total disability will remain in force as long as you remain disabled.  You will be required to submit proof within 6 months of first becoming disabled and ongoing proof of continuing disability will be required on an annual basis.  If We approve the disability as meeting the terms of the Plan, no further premium payments will be required during the continuance of the disability. 

TERMINATION OF INSURANCE
Your insurance coverage under this Plan will terminate on the earliest date upon which any of the following occurs:
--	At the end of the month in which You cease being an active, full-time Employee of the Employer;
--	No longer being eligible for the insurance coverage;
--	Attaining the maximum age for insurance coverage;
--	Termination of the Plan.

DEFINITIONS USED UNDER THE GROUP LIFE PLAN
Some of the common definitions used are as follows:
"Insured Employee" means any employee who is or becomes eligible for insurance.
"You" and "Your" refers to the employee enrolled under the Plan.
"Us", "Our" and "We" refers to W INSURANCE COMPANY Life Insurance
"Total Disability" of an employee means the complete inability to engage in any and every gainful occupation as a result of accidental bodily injury or sickness, while insured under this Plan.
"Salary" of the employee means his/her regular basic pay exclusive of overtime, bonuses and any other form of additional compensation.
"Eligible Employee" means an employee of the Employer who is working regularly throughout the entire duration of the Employer's work week, and in any event not less than 30 hours per week.
A masculine personal pronoun as used herein includes the feminine wherever the context requires.

THE MASTER POLICY IS THE LEGAL DOCUMENT
The material contained in this literature provides a brief explanation of the Plan.  The full terms and conditions of the Plan are set out in the Master Policy issued to Your Employer and the final interpretation of any specific provision will be governed by the Master Policy.
]]></content><Clausetype Id="1"><![CDATA[General provision]]></Clausetype><Title Id="1"><![CDATA[Group Life- Terms and conditions]]></Title><EnumerateSubDocuments Id="14"><![CDATA[No]]></EnumerateSubDocuments><SecondaryDocument Id="17"><![CDATA[No]]></SecondaryDocument><DuringComposition Id="4"><![CDATA[Mandatory]]></DuringComposition><Composed Id="15"><![CDATA[No]]></Composed><Numerotation Id="29"><![CDATA[(0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0)]]></Numerotation><Level Id="30"><![CDATA[0]]></Level><StartOnNextpage Id="36"><![CDATA[No]]></StartOnNextpage><Name Id="3"><![CDATA[Group Life- Terms and conditions]]></Name><MigrationDate Id="15"><![CDATA[--/--/----]]></MigrationDate><NSId Id="1"><![CDATA[318775697]]></NSId><Id Id="2"><![CDATA[23]]></Id><Version Id="3"><![CDATA[1]]></Version></aWLI_StateProvision></EntityExport>