<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<EntityExport><aWLI_StateProvision><States Id="1"><![CDATA[Undefined,AK,AL,AR,AZ,CA,CO,CT,DE,FL,GA,HI,IA,ID,IL,IN,KS,KY,LA,MA,MD,ME,MI,MN,MO,MS,MT,NC,ND,NE,NH,NJ,NM,NV,NY,OH,OK,OR,PA,RI,SC,SD,TN,TX,UT,VA,VT,WA,WI,WV,WY,AS,DC,FM,GU,MH,MP,PW,PR,VI]]></States><Code Id="2"><![CDATA[SCF]]></Code><content Id="4"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\deff0\deflang1036{\fonttbl{\f0\fswiss\fcharset0 Arial;}{\f1\fswiss\fprq2\fcharset0 Calibri;}}
\viewkind4\uc1\pard\lang1033\f0\fs20 We will pay for "loss" to Covered Property from any of the Covered Causes of Loss.\par
\b 1. COVERED PROPERTY, \b0 as used in this Coverage Form, means:\par
\pard\li720\b a. \b0 Your signs; and\par
\b b. \b0 Similar property of others in your care, custody or control.\par
\pard\b 2. PROPERTY NOT COVERED\par
\b0 Covered Property does not include contraband, or property in the course of illegal transportation or trade.\par
\b 3. COVERED CAUSES OF LOSS\par
\b0 Covered Causes of Loss means RISKS OF DIRECT PHYSICAL "LOSS" to Covered Property except those causes of "loss" listed in the Exclusions.\par
\b 4. ADDITIONAL COVERAGE - COLLAPSE\par
\b0 We will pay for direct "loss" caused by or resulting from risks of direct physical "loss" involving collapse of all or part of a building or structure caused by one or more of the following:\par
\b a. \b0 Fire; lightning; windstorm; hail; explosion; smoke; aircraft; vehicles; riot; civil commotion; vandalism; breakage of glass; falling objects; weight of snow, ice or sleet; water damage; all only as covered in this Coverage Form;\par
\b b. \b0 Hidden decay;\par
\b c. \b0 Hidden insect or vermin damage;\par
\b d. \b0 Weight of people or personal property;\par
\b e. \b0 Weight of rain that collects on a roof;\par
\b f. \b0 Use of defective materials or methods in construction, remodeling or renovating if the collapse occurs during the course of the construction, remodeling or renovating.\par
This Additional Coverage does not increase the Limits of Insurance provided in this Coverage Form.\par
\b B. EXCLUSIONS\par
1. \b0 We will not pay for a "loss" caused directly or indirectly by any of the following. Such "loss" is excluded regardless of any other cause or event that contributes concurrently or in any sequence to the "loss."\par
\b a. \b0 Governmental Action\par
Seizure or destruction of property by order of governmental authority.\par
But we will pay for acts of destruction ordered by governmental authority and taken at the time of a fire to prevent its spread if the fire would be covered under this Coverage Form.\par
\b b. \b0 Nuclear Hazard\par
\b (1) \b0 Any weapon employing atomic fission or fusion; or\par
\b (2) \b0 Nuclear reaction or radiation, or radioactive contamination from any other cause. But we will pay for direct "loss" caused by resulting fire if the fire would be covered under this Coverage Form.\par
\b c. \b0 War And Military Action\par
\b (1) \b0 War, including undeclared or civil war;\par
\b (2) \b0 Warlike action by a military force, including action in hindering or defending against an actual or expected attack, by any government, sovereign or other authority using military personnel or other agents; or\par
\b (3) \b0 Insurrection, rebellion, revolution, usurped power or action taken by governmental authority in hindering or defending against any of these.\par
\f1\fs22\par
}
]]></content><Clausetype Id="1"><![CDATA[General provision]]></Clausetype><Title Id="1"><![CDATA[Apartment Building-Signs Coverage Form]]></Title><EnumerateSubDocuments Id="14"><![CDATA[No]]></EnumerateSubDocuments><SecondaryDocument Id="17"><![CDATA[No]]></SecondaryDocument><DuringComposition Id="4"><![CDATA[Mandatory]]></DuringComposition><Composed Id="15"><![CDATA[No]]></Composed><Numerotation Id="29"><![CDATA[(0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0)]]></Numerotation><Level Id="30"><![CDATA[0]]></Level><StartOnNextpage Id="36"><![CDATA[No]]></StartOnNextpage><Name Id="3"><![CDATA[Apartment Building-Signs Coverage Form]]></Name><MigrationDate Id="15"><![CDATA[--/--/----]]></MigrationDate><NSId Id="1"><![CDATA[318775697]]></NSId><Id Id="2"><![CDATA[11]]></Id><Version Id="3"><![CDATA[1]]></Version></aWLI_StateProvision></EntityExport>