<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<EntityExport><aWLI_StateProvision><States Id="1"><![CDATA[Undefined,AK,AL,AR,AZ,CA,CO,CT,DE,FL,GA,HI,IA,ID,IL,IN,KS,KY,LA,MA,MD,ME,MI,MN,MO,MS,MT,NC,ND,NE,NH,NJ,NM,NV,NY,OH,OK,OR,PA,RI,SC,SD,TN,TX,UT,VA,VT,WA,WI,WV,WY,AS,DC,FM,GU,MH,MP,PW,PR,VI]]></States><Code Id="2"><![CDATA[P20]]></Code><content Id="4"><![CDATA[III. PAYMENT OF INSURANCE INDEMNITY
20. Calculation of Insurance Indemnity 
In case of  the Event of Death of  the  Insured  occurring during  time when  the Insurance Cover  is  in  force, except where  the death  is a  result of any of  the causes set out in clause 21 of the Terms and Conditions, the Insurer shall pay Page 2 of
 2
1373T,1.3
01.01.2010
the  Beneficiary  the  Insurance  Indemnity  considering  amount  of  the  Sum Insured in force on the day when the Insured Event occurred.
21. Exceptions
21.1. The  Insurance  Indemnity shall not be paid  if  the death of the  Insured  is related to the following circumstances:
21.1.1. Suicide by the Insured within 2 years following the effective date of the Insurance Contract
21.1.2. driving by the Insured while intoxicated with alcohol, narcotic, psychotropic or other intoxicant substances if concentration thereof in the body exceeds the concentration permitted by laws of the country where the accident happened;
21.1.3. nuclear accident, weapons of mass destruction, warfare, the Insured's participation in mass riots or military operations (military training will not be considered as military operations);
21.1.4. intentional criminal offence by the Insured or the Beneficiary as evidenced by investigation and/or judicial documents;
21.1.5.  If the death of the  Insured occurs due to illness within one year of the Insurance Contract coming into force.
22. Procedure for Payout of Insurance Indemnity
22.1. The Beneficiary shall have a duty  to advise  the  Insurer of  the death of the Insured Person as soon as the Beneficiary becomes aware thereof. Where the  Beneficiary  is  a minor,  the  duty  to  advise  the  Insurer  shall  lie  with  the Guardia
n of the Beneficiary.
22.2. In order for the Insurer to cause payout of the Insurance Indemnity in the Event  of  Death  of  the  Insured,  the  Beneficiary,  in  person  or  through  third parties, shall  file a  relevant application and  the  following documents with  the In
surer:
- a copy of passport or other proof of identity (having produced the original documents);
- a copy of Insurance Policy where requested so by the Insurer; 
- a copy of certificate of  inheritance by  the presentation of original document  (if  the  documents  are  filed  by  the  inheritor  of  the Beneficiary);
- copy  of  certificate  of  death  of  the  Insured  (having  produced  the original document);
- a report on the cause of death;
- a copy of medical history of the Insured where requested so by the Insurer.
- in  case  of  the  Insured's  violent  death,  suicide,  sudden  death  or death  resulting  from  an  accident,  a  decision  from  investigation institutions  and  /  or  court  documents  and/or  forensic  medicine expert's  or  commission's  formal 
 opinion  on  the  causes  and conditions of death.
22.3. The  Insurer shall decide on payout of the  Insurance  Indemnity within 5 (five)  business  days  of  receiving  all  the  documents  required  under  the Insurance  Contract. The  Insurer  shall  have  the  right  to  extend  the  above period if o
bjective reasons to do so exist.
The Insurer shall not be obliged to pay out any  Insurance  Indemnity until and unless  information about  the death of  Insured  and  the necessary documents are  provided. In  case  the Beneficiary  or  their Guardian  deliberately  violates their  duti
es  and  fails  to  advise  the  Insurer  of  the  death  of  the  Insured,  or 
deliberately does not supply the documents listed in clause 22.1 of the Terms and Conditions,  the  Insurer shall have no obligation to pay out the  Insurance Indemnity.
22.4. If the performance of insurer's obligations, or the extent thereof, depends on the circumstances, which are found in civil, criminal or administrative proceedings or in the proceedings for breach of administrative law, the Insurer will be entitled t
o decide on the payment or refusal of insurance indemnity after the suspension, termination of the proceeding or after the decision of the court or appropriate officials comes into force.
22.5. In case of concurrent death of the Insured and of the Beneficiary or if the death  of  the  Beneficiary  occurs  after  the  death  of  the  Insured  and  before payout of  the  Insurance  Indemnity,  then, pursuant  to  the  Insurance Contract, the
 entitlement  to  receive  the  Insurance  Indemnity  shall  pass  to  the heirs  of the Beneficiary, who shall be required to present  the certificate of inheritance unless the Insurance Contract stipulates otherwise.
]]></content><Clausetype Id="1"><![CDATA[General provision]]></Clausetype><Title Id="1"><![CDATA[III. PAYMENT OF INSURANCE INDEMNITY]]></Title><EnumerateSubDocuments Id="14"><![CDATA[No]]></EnumerateSubDocuments><SecondaryDocument Id="17"><![CDATA[No]]></SecondaryDocument><DuringComposition Id="4"><![CDATA[Mandatory]]></DuringComposition><Composed Id="15"><![CDATA[No]]></Composed><Numerotation Id="29"><![CDATA[(0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0)]]></Numerotation><Level Id="30"><![CDATA[0]]></Level><StartOnNextpage Id="36"><![CDATA[No]]></StartOnNextpage><Name Id="3"><![CDATA[Terms and conditions III]]></Name><MigrationDate Id="15"><![CDATA[--/--/----]]></MigrationDate><NSId Id="1"><![CDATA[318775697]]></NSId><Id Id="2"><![CDATA[40]]></Id><Version Id="3"><![CDATA[1]]></Version></aWLI_StateProvision></EntityExport>