<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<EntityExport><aWLI_StateProvision><States Id="1"><![CDATA[Undefined,AK,AL,AR,AZ,CA,CO,CT,DE,FL,GA,HI,IA,ID,IL,IN,KS,KY,LA,MA,MD,ME,MI,MN,MO,MS,MT,NC,ND,NE,NH,NJ,NM,NV,NY,OH,OK,OR,PA,RI,SC,SD,TN,TX,UT,VA,VT,WA,WI,WV,WY,AS,DC,FM,GU,MH,MP,PW,PR,VI]]></States><Code Id="2"><![CDATA[P21]]></Code><content Id="4"><![CDATA[I TERMS AND DEFINITIONS
1. Insurance Contract
means an agreement between the Policyholder and the Insurer whereby:
-  the  Policyholder  agrees  to  pay  the  Insurance  Premium  at  an  extent  and 
according to the procedure set forth in the Insurance Contract, and
-  the  Insurer agrees  to pay  the  Insurance  Indemnity  in  the events and at  the 
extent set forth in the Insurance Contract.
2. Insurance Policy
means  the  document  issued  by  the  Insurer  as  a  proof  of  entry  into  the 
Insurance Contract.
3. Insurer
means  Swedbank  Life  insurance  SE (hereinafter  alternatively  referred  to  as 
"Swedbank  Life  Insurance")  represented  by  the  tied  insurance  agent 
Swedbank AS.
4. Policyholder
means  the natural person specified in  the Insurance Contract who enters  into 
the Insurance Contract with the Insurer.
5. Insured
means  a  natural  person,  whose  life  is  being  insured  and  who  is  also  the 
Policyholder.
At  the  time of entering  in  the  Insurance Contract,  the  Insured must 18  to 50
years of age. At the end of the insurance period - not older  than 55 years of 
age.
6. Guardian
means  the  natural  guardians  (parents)  of  the  Beneficiary,  the  guardian 
appointed  by  the  Orphans  Court  or  by  other  competent  institution,  or  the 
adopter approved by court.
7. Bank
means Swedbank AS.
8. Account
means the Policyholder's account specified in the Insurance Contract.
9. Beneficiary
means  the  natural  person  stated  in  the  Insurance  Contract,  to  whom  the 
Insurer  agrees  to  pay  the  Insurance  Indemnity  upon  occurrence  of  Insured 
Event. The Policyholder may  change  the Beneficiary  during  the  term  of  the 
Insurance Contract by filing a written application to the Insurer.
10. Insured Event
means  the death of the  Insured during the time when the  Insurance Cover  is 
in  force (the "Event of Death of the  Insured"). The insured's death during the 
time,  when  the  insurance  cover  has  been  suspended  or  terminated,  is  not 
considered an Insured Event.
11. Insurance Cover
is  the  insurer's  liability upon occurrence of  the  Insured Event during  the  time 
when  the  Insurance Cover  is  in  force  to  pay  the  Insurance  Indemnity  in  an 
amount and under conditions determined by the Insurance Contract.
12. Sum Insured
means the amount of money, at the extent of which the life of the Insured is 
insured. The Sum Insured is equivalent to employees' monthly average gross 
pay, as determined by the Central Statistics Board of the Republic of Latvia in 
the last quarter of the previous calendar year, multiplied by 12.
The amount of the Sum Insured is reviewed annually on 1 April.
13. Insurance Indemnity
means the amount of money paid to the Beneficiary upon occurrence of an 
Event Insured. If an Insured Event occurs as a result of a traffic accident, the 
payment of the Insurance Indemnity will be equivalent to two Sums Insured.
14. Insurance Premium
means  the payment  that  the Policyholder  has  a duty  to make  to  the  Insurer 
under  the  Insurance  Contract. The  Insurance  Premium  varies  during  the 
contract in accordance with changes in the Sum Insured.
15. Insurance Contract Currency
for  payment  of  Insurance  Premiums  and  the  Insurance  Indemnity  shall  be 
Latvian lats.
16. Road Traffic Accident
means an accident,  in  road  traffic or other place where motoring  is possible, 
where at least one vehicle  is involved and which has resulted  in  the death of 
the Insured as evidenced by investigation and / or court documents.
]]></content><Clausetype Id="1"><![CDATA[General provision]]></Clausetype><Title Id="1"><![CDATA[I TERMS AND DEFINITIONS]]></Title><EnumerateSubDocuments Id="14"><![CDATA[No]]></EnumerateSubDocuments><SecondaryDocument Id="17"><![CDATA[No]]></SecondaryDocument><DuringComposition Id="4"><![CDATA[Mandatory]]></DuringComposition><Composed Id="15"><![CDATA[No]]></Composed><Numerotation Id="29"><![CDATA[(0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0)]]></Numerotation><Level Id="30"><![CDATA[0]]></Level><StartOnNextpage Id="36"><![CDATA[No]]></StartOnNextpage><Name Id="3"><![CDATA[Terms and conditions-Definitions]]></Name><MigrationDate Id="15"><![CDATA[--/--/----]]></MigrationDate><NSId Id="1"><![CDATA[318775697]]></NSId><Id Id="2"><![CDATA[41]]></Id><Version Id="3"><![CDATA[1]]></Version></aWLI_StateProvision></EntityExport>