<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<EntityExport><aWLI_StateProvision><States Id="1"><![CDATA[Undefined,AK,AL,AR,AZ,CA,CO,CT,DE,FL,GA,HI,IA,ID,IL,IN,KS,KY,LA,MA,MD,ME,MI,MN,MO,MS,MT,NC,ND,NE,NH,NJ,NM,NV,NY,OH,OK,OR,PA,RI,SC,SD,TN,TX,UT,VA,VT,WA,WI,WV,WY,AS,DC,FM,GU,MH,MP,PW,PR,VI]]></States><Code Id="2"><![CDATA[P22]]></Code><content Id="4"><![CDATA[II. ENTRY INTO AND VALIDITY OF THE CONTRACT
17. Entry into the Contract
17.1. The Policyholder shall have the right to enter into the Insurance Contract via  the  online  banking  facility,  provided  that  the  Policyholder  and  the  Bank have entered into the "Remote Banking Services Agreement".
17.2. The present terms and conditions of insurance ("Terms and Conditions") 
and the Insurance Policy constitute an integral part of the Insurance Contract.
The  Policyholder,  by  signing  the  Insurance  Policy  or  by  entering  into Insurance Contract by via remote means of communication, confirms  that the Policyholder has received and has read the aforesaid documents.
18. Insurance Cover
18.1.  The  Insurance  Contract  shall  be  deemed  concluded  on  the  date  of signing  the  Insurance  Policy  or  of  entering  into  the  Insurance  Contract  via remote means  of  communication. The  Insurance  Coverage  shall  come  into force at t
he time of entering into the Insurance Contract. The Insurance Cover 
shall be valid on a 24-hour basis in any country of the world.
18.2. Unless stated otherwise in  the Insurance Contract,  the  Insurance Cover shall expire:
18.2.1. at 24:00 hours on the date of expiration of the Insurance Contract;
18.2.2. at 24:00 hours on the day stated by the Policyholder in the application for early termination of the Insurance Contract;
18.2.3. when  the event set  forth  in clause 19.3 of  the Terms and Conditions has occurred.
19. Payment of Insurance Premium
19.1. Upon entering  into  Insurance Contract,  the Policyholder agrees with the Insurer  on  regular monthly  Insurance Premium  payments  on  the  1st  date  of each month through direct debit.
19.2.  If the first  Insurance Premium is not received within 3 (three) days after the latest payment date stipulated in  the  Insurance Contract,  the  Insurer shall suspend  Insurance Cover  on  the  4th  (fourth)  day  at  00.00  hours.  Insurance 
Cover  shall  be  restored  on  the  next  day's  00.00  hours  after  payment  of Insurance Premium in full. If the first Insurance Premium is not received within 60  days  of  the  Insurance Contract  having  been  entered  into,  the  Insurance Contrac
t  shall  be deemed  null and  void  as  from  the moment  it was  entered 
into, and the Insurer shall have the right terminate the Insurance Contract.
19.3. If any further Insurance Premium payment is not met according to clause 
19.1 as it falls due and payable, the Insurer shall notify the Policyholder of the date  until  which  the  Policyholder  will  be  obligated  to  pay  the  overdue 
Insurance Premium payment. Along with giving  the such a notice, the  Insurer shall advise  the Policyholder  of  the consequences of  incomplete payment of the Insurance Premium.
Should  the Policyholder  fail  to pay  the  Insurance Premium on or  before  the date and at  the extent  fixed  in  the notice on  incomplete  Insurance Premium payment, the Insurer shall suspend Insurance Cover after the day fixed as due for  the outst
anding payment  in  the notice on  incomplete  Insurance Premium 
payment. Should  the  Policyholder  fail  to  meet  the  Insurance  Premium payments  that  would  be  sufficient  for  covering  the  overdue  Insurance Premium payments and the current Insurance Premium payment until the date of  termination  of  the  I
nsurance Contract  stated  in  the  notice  on  incomplete Insurance  Premium  payment,  the  Insurer  shall  terminate  the  Insurance Contract.
The  Insurance Cover  shall  be  restored and  the  Insurance Contract  shall  not be  terminated  on  the  day  stated  in  the  Insurer's  notice  on  incomplete Insurance Premium payment if the overdue Insurance Premium payments and the current Insuran
ce Premium payment are made on or before that date.
19.4.  The  Policyholder,  by  signing  the  Insurance  Contract,  authorizes  the Bank to debit  the Insurance Premium payments required under the Insurance Contract  from  the  Policyholder's  bank  account  specified  in  the  Insurance Contract. The  
Policyholder  shall,  on  the  date  due  for  Insurance  Premium 
payment  required under  the  Insurance Contract,  cause  the Account  to have an amount of money sufficient  for meeting  the  Insurance Premium payment required under  the  Insurance Contract. Should  the amount of money on  the Account be not sufficien
t to transfer the Insurance Premium payment in full on the date when  the  Insurance Premium  falls due and payable,  the Bank shall not transfer the relevant  Insurance Premium payment, nevertheless  the Bank shall  be entitled  to  transfer  the  Insura
nce Premium  payment when  there are sufficient  funds  on  the Account  to meet  the  Insurance Premium  payment  in full. The  responsibility  for  paying  the  Insurance Premium as  it  falls  due and payable shall lie with the Policyholder.
The  Bank  shall  be  entitled  to  convert  funds  held  in  any  currency  into  the currency of  the  Insurance Contract at  the exchange  rate of  the Bank  then  in force.
In  case  the Bank,  pursuant  to  the Policyholder's  instructions,  is  required  to effect a number of payments,  the Bank shall have  the  right  to determine  the order  of  such  payments  as  it  may  deem  appropriate. Insurance  Premiums shall be
 deemed paid when they are credited to the account of the Insurer.
]]></content><Clausetype Id="1"><![CDATA[General provision]]></Clausetype><Title Id="1"><![CDATA[II. ENTRY INTO AND VALIDITY OF THE CONTRACT]]></Title><EnumerateSubDocuments Id="14"><![CDATA[No]]></EnumerateSubDocuments><SecondaryDocument Id="17"><![CDATA[No]]></SecondaryDocument><DuringComposition Id="4"><![CDATA[Mandatory]]></DuringComposition><Composed Id="15"><![CDATA[No]]></Composed><Numerotation Id="29"><![CDATA[(0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0)]]></Numerotation><Level Id="30"><![CDATA[0]]></Level><StartOnNextpage Id="36"><![CDATA[No]]></StartOnNextpage><Name Id="3"><![CDATA[Terms and conditions-II]]></Name><MigrationDate Id="15"><![CDATA[--/--/----]]></MigrationDate><NSId Id="1"><![CDATA[318775697]]></NSId><Id Id="2"><![CDATA[42]]></Id><Version Id="3"><![CDATA[1]]></Version></aWLI_StateProvision></EntityExport>