<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<EntityExport><aWLI_StateProvision><States Id="1"><![CDATA[Undefined,AK,AL,AR,AZ,CA,CO,CT,DE,FL,GA,HI,IA,ID,IL,IN,KS,KY,LA,MA,MD,ME,MI,MN,MO,MS,MT,NC,ND,NE,NH,NJ,NM,NV,NY,OH,OK,OR,PA,RI,SC,SD,TN,TX,UT,VA,VT,WA,WI,WV,WY,AS,DC,FM,GU,MH,MP,PW,PR,VI]]></States><Code Id="2"><![CDATA[P23]]></Code><content Id="4"><![CDATA[IV.  OTHER CONDITIONS OF THE CONTRACT
23. Amendment of insurance contract
23.1.  The  Policyholder  and  Insurer  may  have  the  Insurance  Contract amended as and when agreed so in writing.
23.2.  The  Insurer  and  the  Policyholder  shall  confirm  amendments  to  the Insurance  Contract  by  signing  those,  unless  stipulated  otherwise  in  the Insurance Contract.
23.3. The Insurer shall stipulate which types of amendments to the Insurance 
Contract may be made  remotely  via online banking  facility, provided  that  the Policyholder  and  the Bank have  entered  into  the  "Remote Banking Services Agreement".
24. Termination of Insurance Contract
24. 1. The Policyholder  shall  be entitled  to  terminate  the  Insurance Contract unilaterally. In  such  an  event  the  party  wishing  to  terminate  the  Insurance Contract shall be required to deliver a relevant written application to the other par
ty. The Insurance Contract shall be terminated on the day of receiving  the 
application for termination of the Insurance Contract.
24.2. In case of termination of the Insurance Contract no insurance premiums paid shall be refunded except as stipulated in clause 24.3.
24.3. The Policyholder shall have the right to terminate the Insurance Contract within 15 days of the day  the  Insurance Contract was entered into (where  the Insurance Contract was entered into via remote means of communication, the Policyholder  shall 
 be entitled  to exercise  their  right  of withdrawal,  namely  to 
terminate  the  Insurance  Contract  within  30  (thirty)  days  of  the  day  the Insurance  Contract  was  entered  into). In  such  an  event  the  Insurer  shall refund to  the Policyholder  the  Insurance Premium paid by the Policyholder  in full. To
 terminate the Insurance Contract, the Policyholder shall give a relevant 
written notice to the Insurer thereof.
25. Liability of the Parties and Exchange of Information
25.1. The Policyholder,  upon entry  into  the  Insurance Contract,  shall have a duty  to  provide  the  Insurer  with  all  and  any  information  requested  by  the Insurer.
25.2. If the Policyholder, at the time of entry into the Insurance Contract has provided the Insurer with false information about the circumstances, which are material for the assessment of probability of occurrence of the insured risk, or has deliberatel
y withheld the relevant information, the Insurance Contract shall be deemed null and void as from the moment it was entered into. No 
Insurance Premiums paid shall be refunded in such an event.
25.3. The Policyholder undertakes to keep the Insurer informed in written from during the Insurance Contract about any changes in the Policyholder's contact details or personal details given  in  the  Insurance Policy. Such changes shall 
be enclosed with the Insurance Contract.
25. 4. All and any notifications  and applications  to  the  Insurer  related  to  the Insurance Contract shall be submitted in such a form and in such a manner as to  enable  the  Insurer  to  identify  the  person  giving  the  notification  or  the app
lication.
25.5. The  Insurer shall send  their notices and  information  to  the Policyholder by  post  to  the  latest  address  notified  by  the  Policyholder. In  case  of  the Policyholder  changing  their  mailing  address  without  informing  the  Insurer th
ereof, all notices shall be deemed received on the 5 (fifth) day following  the delivery of the relevant consignment to the post office. If the Policyholder has notified  the  Insurer of  their e-mail address,  the  Insurer shall have  the  right  to send
  its notices  to  the e-mail address given by  the Policyholder, which shall be  deemed  equivalent  to  sending  the  notice  to  the  Policyholder's  mailing address. The  Insurer  shall  have  the  right  to  send  information  and  notices pertaining
  to  the  Insurance Contract also  via online banking  facility, provided that the Insurer and the Bank have entered into the "Remote Banking Services Agreement". The  Insurer  shall  have  the  right  advise  the  Policyholder  of changes in its contact
 details via mass media.
26. Personal Data
26. 1. The Insurer shall be liable for processing of personal data.
26.2. The processing of personal data  is necessary  for  the  Insurer  for  entry into  the  Insurance  Contract  and  for  performance  of  obligations  under  the Insurance  Contract. The  Insurer  is  the  controller  of  the  registered  personal dat
a processing system, and the Bank is the personal data operator.
26.3.  After  expiration  the  Insurance  Contract  and  when  the  obligations between the Insurer and the Policyholder have ceased to exist, and the data is no longer necessary for  their purpose of processing, the Policyholder, who is also  the  Insure
d,  shall have  the  right  to  demand  that  their  personal data be 
removed  from electronic databases and  that  the processing of  their personal data be discontinued.
26.4. The Policyholder, who  is also  the  Insured,  shall  have  the  right, at  any time, to demand correction, addition or modification of their personal data, as well as  to demand provision of  information about and access  to  the personal data that
 is processed regarding this person.
27. Dispute Settlement
27.1. The Parties shall be guided by legislation of the Republic of Latvia in the entry into and performance of the Insurance Contract.
27.2. In case any provision of the Insurance Contract is deemed invalid due to it being at variance with the applicable legislation, it will not constitute grounds to invalidate the entire Insurance Contract or other provisions of the Insurance Contract.
27.3. All matters not contemplated  in  the  Insurance Contract, as well as any dispute, disagreement or claim arising  from  the  Insurance Contract, affecting the  Insurance Contract,  or  the  amendment,  breach,  termination,  lawfulness, validity, or
  interpretation of  the  Insurance Contract shall be  resolved  through negotiation.
27.4.  In  case  no  resolution  is  reached  through  negotiation,  the  dispute  in question shall, at  the discretion of  the claimant, be  referred  to court of  law  in accordance with legislation in force in the United States. 
]]></content><Clausetype Id="1"><![CDATA[General provision]]></Clausetype><Title Id="1"><![CDATA[IV.  OTHER CONDITIONS OF THE CONTRACT]]></Title><EnumerateSubDocuments Id="14"><![CDATA[No]]></EnumerateSubDocuments><SecondaryDocument Id="17"><![CDATA[No]]></SecondaryDocument><DuringComposition Id="4"><![CDATA[Mandatory]]></DuringComposition><Composed Id="15"><![CDATA[No]]></Composed><Numerotation Id="29"><![CDATA[(0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0)]]></Numerotation><Level Id="30"><![CDATA[0]]></Level><StartOnNextpage Id="36"><![CDATA[No]]></StartOnNextpage><Name Id="3"><![CDATA[Terms and donctions IV]]></Name><MigrationDate Id="15"><![CDATA[--/--/----]]></MigrationDate><NSId Id="1"><![CDATA[318775697]]></NSId><Id Id="2"><![CDATA[43]]></Id><Version Id="3"><![CDATA[1]]></Version></aWLI_StateProvision></EntityExport>