<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<EntityExport><aWLI_StateProvision><States Id="1"><![CDATA[Undefined,AK,AL,AR,AZ,CA,CO,CT,DE,FL,GA,HI,IA,ID,IL,IN,KS,KY,LA,MA,MD,ME,MI,MN,MO,MS,MT,NC,ND,NE,NH,NJ,NM,NV,NY,OH,OK,OR,PA,RI,SC,SD,TN,TX,UT,VA,VT,WA,WI,WV,WY,AS,DC,FM,GU,MH,MP,PW,PR,VI]]></States><Code Id="2"><![CDATA[P9]]></Code><content Id="4"><![CDATA[SUPPLEMENT TO GROUP LIFE POLICY AND SUBJECT TO THE TERMS & CONDITIONS OF THE GROUP LIFE POLICY


ACCIDENTAL DEATH AND DISMEMBERMENT INSURANCE

BENEFITS PAYABLE
Injury means bodily injury caused solely by external, violent and accidental means.
If You suffer a bodily injury caused by an accident and as a direct result of such injury and, to the exclusion of all other causes, sustain within 365 days of the accident any of the losses listed in the Schedule of Losses below, and provided:
(a)	the injury occurs while insurance is in force for You;
(b)	the loss resulting from the injury is not excluded from coverage; and
(c)	the loss has continued for twelve (12) consecutive months and the Loss of Use (as defined) is determined to be permanent by Your medical physician
We shall, subject to the terms of the Plan, pay a benefit in accordance with the Schedule of Benefits but in no case shall more than the Sum Insured be paid for all losses sustained by You through any one accident.
Schedule of Losses

 
LOSS OF:	BENEFIT AMOUNT
	   
Life	The Sum Insured stated on the Certificate's Schedule of Benefits	   
Both Hands or both feet or both arms or both
Legs or sight of both eyes or any combination
Of losses mentioned above	The Sum Insured stated on the Certificate's Schedule of Benefits	   
One hand or one arm or one leg or one foot
Or the sight of one eye	50% of the Sum Insured stated on the Certificate's Schedule of Benefits	 

LOSS OF shall mean:
(i)	with regard to arms and legs, dismemberment through or above the elbow or knee joints.
(ii)	with regard to hands and feet, dismemberment through or above the wrist and ankle joints but below the elbow or knee joints.
(iii)	with regard to sight, the entire irrevocable loss beyond any remedy or partial remedy by surgical or other means.

TOTAL USE OF means:
 
Both arms or both legs (Quadriplegia)	The Sum Insured stated on the Certificate's
Schedule of Benefits	   
Both arms (Paraplegia)	The Sum Insured stated on the Certificate's
Schedule of Benefits	   
Both legs (Paraplegia)	The Sum Insured stated on the Certificate's
Schedule of Benefits	   
One arm and one leg or one side of the body (Hemiplegia)	The Sum Insured stated on the Certificate's
Schedule of Benefits	 

The 12 Consecutive month waiting period will be waived if the permanent Total Loss of Use is due solely to complete and irreversible paralysis, as defined:
QUADRIPLEGIA means total and irrecoverable paralysis of both the upper and lower limbs.
HEMIPLEGIA means total and irrecoverable paralysis of the upper and lower limbs on one side of the body.
PARAPLEGIA means total and irrecoverable paralysis of both lower limbs.
EXPOSURE & DISAPPEARANCE
If by reason of an accident (not having been caused by Your deliberate act or omission) occurring while Your coverage is in force under the Plan, You are unavoidably exposed to the elements and as a result of such exposure, suffer a loss, the loss will be covered under the terms of the Plan.
If Your body has not been found within 365 days of the disappearance, forced landing, stranding, sinking or wrecking of a conveyance in which You were an occupant while covered under the Policy, then it will be deemed, subject to all other terms and provisions of the Plan and unless there is reasonable evidence to the contrary, that You have suffered an accidental death.
repatriation benefit

No benefit shall be payable in respect of any loss caused directly or indirectly, wholly or in part by one or more of the following:
1.	Bodily or mental illness, infirmity or disease of any kind, or by medical or surgical treatment thereof; or
2.	Ptomaines or bacterial infections (except pyogenic infections occurring with and through an accidental cut or wound), or hernia, or medical or surgical treatment therefore; or
3.	Attempted suicide or intentional self-destruction whether sane or insane; or
4.	War or act of war, declared or undeclared; or
5.	Voluntary participation in a riot or insurrection, or as the result of the commission of or attempt to commit an assault or felony; or
6.	Activity while on duty as a member of any military organization; or
7.	Participation in flying, bungee jumping, ballooning, hand-gliding, parachuting, or other aeronautic activities, except as a fare paying passenger on a licensed commercial aircraft which is operated by a licensed pilot on a regular passenger route; or
8.	The voluntary use of any drug, narcotic, or hallucinogen, except as prescribed by a licensed physician; or
9.	Driving while intoxicated as defined by the applicable laws of Minnesota.


]]></content><Clausetype Id="1"><![CDATA[General provision]]></Clausetype><Title Id="1"><![CDATA[ACCIDENTAL DEATH AND DISMEMBERMENT INSURANCE]]></Title><EnumerateSubDocuments Id="14"><![CDATA[No]]></EnumerateSubDocuments><SecondaryDocument Id="17"><![CDATA[No]]></SecondaryDocument><DuringComposition Id="4"><![CDATA[Mandatory]]></DuringComposition><Composed Id="15"><![CDATA[No]]></Composed><Numerotation Id="29"><![CDATA[(0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0)]]></Numerotation><Level Id="30"><![CDATA[0]]></Level><StartOnNextpage Id="36"><![CDATA[No]]></StartOnNextpage><Name Id="3"><![CDATA[Group Life-AD&D]]></Name><MigrationDate Id="15"><![CDATA[--/--/----]]></MigrationDate><NSId Id="1"><![CDATA[318775697]]></NSId><Id Id="2"><![CDATA[24]]></Id><Version Id="3"><![CDATA[1]]></Version></aWLI_StateProvision></EntityExport>