<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<EntityExport><aWLI_StateProvision><States Id="1"><![CDATA[Undefined,AK,AL,AR,AZ,CA,CO,CT,DE,FL,GA,HI,IA,ID,IL,IN,KS,KY,LA,MA,MD,ME,MI,MN,MO,MS,MT,NC,ND,NE,NH,NJ,NM,NV,NY,OH,OK,OR,PA,RI,SC,SD,TN,TX,UT,VA,VT,WA,WI,WV,WY,AS,DC,FM,GU,MH,MP,PW,PR,VI]]></States><Code Id="2"><![CDATA[VPF]]></Code><content Id="4"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\deff0\deflang1036{\fonttbl{\f0\fnil\fcharset0 MS Sans Serif;}{\f1\fnil MS Sans Serif;}}
{\colortbl ;\red0\green0\blue0;}
\viewkind4\uc1\pard\cf1\b\f0\fs16 INTRODUCTION\b0\f1\par
The Insurance Services Office (ISO) Valuable Papers And Records Coverage Form insures against direct physical loss or damage to covered property except for causes of loss indicated in Exclusions. It covers losses to inscribed, printed or written documents, manuscripts or records and abstracts, books, deeds, drawings, films, maps and mortgages.\par
This coverage form is not used as much as in the past because valuable papers and records coverage is an additional coverage or an extension of coverage with significant sub-limits in many filed commercial property coverage forms and policies. Businessowners and Capital Assets policies have significant sub-limits for valuable papers and records coverage and many independently filed company commercial property coverage forms and policies also include significant valuable papers and records coverage sub-limits as an extension of coverage. However, valuable papers and records coverage should not be dismissed or treated as unnecessary before thoroughly and carefully reviewing it. The coverage provided is usually broader than that offered as an additional coverage or an extension of coverage in most commercial property coverage forms.\par
\b\f0 POLICY CONSTRUCTION\b0\f1\par
The following forms are mandatory:\par
CM DS 02\f0 -Commercial Inland Marine Declarations\par
IL 00 17-Common Policy Conditions\par
CM 00 01-Commercial Inland Marine Conditions\par
CM DS 17-Valuable Papers And Records Declarations\par
CM 00 67-Valuable Papers And Records Coverage Form\par
Note: Valuable papers and records coverage may be issued as a stand-alone, monoline inland marine policy or as part of a commercial package policy.\par
\b ELIGIBILITY\b0\par
Valuable papers and records are broadly defined. They include documents that are inscribed, printed or written as well as manuscripts. Records covered include, but are not limited to, books, abstracts, deeds, drawing, films, maps and mortgages. Any party that owns valuable papers or has valuable papers of others in its care, custody or control is eligible.\par
CM DS 17-VALUABLE PAPERS AND RECORDS DECLARATIONS\par
CM DS 17-Valuable Papers And Records Declarations does not have a place for the name, mailing address and other named insured identifying information because that information is contained in CM DS 02-Commercial Inland Marine Declarations. CM DS 17-Valuable Papers And Records \par
\b Deductible\b0\par
The standard $500 deductible the named insured retains for each covered loss applies unless a different amount is entered in the space provided.\f1\par
}
]]></content><Clausetype Id="1"><![CDATA[General provision]]></Clausetype><Title Id="1"><![CDATA[Apartment Building-Valuable Papers and Records Form]]></Title><EnumerateSubDocuments Id="14"><![CDATA[No]]></EnumerateSubDocuments><SecondaryDocument Id="17"><![CDATA[No]]></SecondaryDocument><DuringComposition Id="4"><![CDATA[Mandatory]]></DuringComposition><Composed Id="15"><![CDATA[No]]></Composed><Numerotation Id="29"><![CDATA[(0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0)]]></Numerotation><Level Id="30"><![CDATA[0]]></Level><StartOnNextpage Id="36"><![CDATA[No]]></StartOnNextpage><Name Id="3"><![CDATA[Apartment Building-Valuable Papers and Records Form]]></Name><MigrationDate Id="15"><![CDATA[--/--/----]]></MigrationDate><NSId Id="1"><![CDATA[318775697]]></NSId><Id Id="2"><![CDATA[13]]></Id><Version Id="3"><![CDATA[1]]></Version></aWLI_StateProvision></EntityExport>